Allahu Akbar
La Elaha Ella Allah
Alhamdu Lillah, Wa Ash-hadu Alla Elaha Ella Allah Wahdahu La Shareeka Lah.
Praise be to God. We bear witness that there is no god except
the One God.
We are a very fortunate generation. And this is understatement of the year. In SURA 32
God says that certain people have no
idea how much joy and happiness await them. And we have no idea
how fortunate we are, but 50 years from now, the future generation will realize how fortunate
we are. We are the pioneers of something that is very special.
About 50 years ago, for example, God's miracles through his messengers existed without any proof.
And even now our generation, excluding the pioneers, that
we have become, you go to them and say Moses threw down the
staff and it became a snake. And they say sure. Oh, yeah,
sure. The unbelievers. Even the believers have doubts. You tell them Jesus revived the
dead. And they say oh, maybe, he just fainted or something or he was just,
you know, he was sick or something and he came back to life. They do not believe those
miracles. But now, God gives us the first tangible evidence that when Moses
threw down the staff, it became a snake. Because what we have, and turns out that this has been
always the case in the scriptures, in the Bible, in the Old Testament, the New Testament,
everything that God sent down, everything that God created you and
me and the Sun, the moon, the stars, they all have God's signature on them.
The scriptures are mathematically composed, numerically structured beyond human intelligence.
So, every statement in the Quran becomes proven with
physical evidence. So, when the Quran makes the statement; Moses threw down the staff
and became a snake, this becomes a physical evidence proving it
because it is mathematically composed by God Himself. It is authenticated by the mathematical
composition that comes only from God, not from a human being.
And God was an eyewitness there. God was an eyewitness who saw Moses throw down the staff
and it became a snake. And He's telling us
in a numerically-structured statement. And the same is true with.
Jesus revived the dead. Every statement in the Quran
is physically proven beyond doubt. So, that's how this is
the fortune that we are not aware of. And this is how fortunate we are, is that we have
now, you read the Quran, and you have full confidence in everything it
says, including many things that are unbelievable, like Moses throwing down the staff and having
it turn into a snake. God says in Quran in SURA 41, verse 53
I will increase My evidence. I will continuously increase My evidence until everyone believes
that this is the truth. So, when, I'm going to talk to you today about
the miracle of Quran again because there's some new evidence that just came out confirming
this statement of God that He will increase His evidence. So, initially we
said that the first verse in Quran consisted of 19 letters. And the number of SURAs 114
is a multiple of 19. And they said well, this is coincidence. This is when
this came out first. And then, we found out that in SURA entitled Q,
there are 57 Qs. The other, the only other SURA initialed with Q also had 57 Qs.
19 x 3 and 19 x 3. 19 letters in the first verse. 19 x 6, the Quran SURAs, and
people said coincidence. Then, we found out that if you add these two 57, 57
you have 114. 'Q' stands for QURAN. 114 SURAs. And they said this is coincidence. They still
continued to disbelieve. And then, we said that this statement here
which is 19 letters. Every word of it is found in the Quran in multiples of 19.
The first word is 19 times. The second word 2698 times. The third word 57 times.
The fourth word 114 times. And they said this is coincidence. So, God kept increasing the evidence
and you know the rest. You know that the letter 'NOON' in
SURA 'NuN' is 133, a multiple of 19. You know
that we have, I'm just reminding you of a few
of those. So, you will be the people who appreciate the Masjid Tucson
miracle more than anybody else. There are seven
SURAs initialed with HA MEEM, H. M.,
seven chapters constituting about one-tenth of the Quran. And you count these
letters in the seven chapters and you'll have 2147 of these letters in the seven chapters.
This is 19 x 113. If only one HA, one H, or one M was lost or added or
substituted in the last 1400 years, this will increase by one or decrease by one. And the
whole thing disappears. The whole thing collapses. So, you can
see the mathematical composition that is beyond human intelligence and has to be from God.
The thing that gives you confidence that when Moses threw down
the staff, it became a snake. It's as like you're an eyewitness. You're just as good as
an eyewitness if not better. When Moses threw down the staff and became
a snake, how many people saw that? Very few people who were inside the palace hall with Pharaoh.
And how long did it last? A few minutes and that was it. That was the
end of it. The miracle happened. A few people saw it. It was over in a few minutes.
But this miracle of Quran is continuous forever. It is perpetual. It is doing two things.
It is a continuous miracle until the end of the world.
And it confirms all those temporary miracles that were limited by time and space
like Jesus reviving the dead.
How long did it take for Jesus to revive Lazarus? How many people saw Jesus revive Lazarus?
But now, we know. Now, we are witnessing that miracle now, millions of people
by mathematically-composed statements, authenticated by God Himself.
We know that this is not man-made. God wrote that, and He was an eyewitness.
So, when this came out, they said we don't believe it.
I just received a review written by something, something Phillip. Phillip is the last name.
He's not our Phillip here. Some other Phillip. And they finally admitted that there are four or five SURAs
that, are, actually have multiples of 19.
What they admitted was the Qs
that these are 57 in each of the Q-initialed SURAs. So, that's two SURAs.
The N in SURA 68. They said yes, this is correct. The YA SEEN, YS-initialed SURA,
SURA 19, K. H. Y. 'A. S., five initials. What was the other SURA?
I think this is it. And they said this is not enough to establish a pattern. It is pure coincidence.
So, they don't, they don't... But at least, finally they admitted that there is
something here. About the H.M. SURAs, they said why is he adding them together?
And they raised all kinds of strange questions. So, what you'll see in the next issue of the Muslim Perspective,
not this one, not October, but November, is that
it is obvious that God is increasing His evidence just as He said in chapter 41.
And that those people will continue to say no, we don't believe
in order to expose and confirm the hardcore unbelievers who will end up in the lowest pit of Hell.
The reason... the reason I'm saying this is that Lisa, yesterday, found something else.
This KHUTBA should be given by Lisa by the way but this fits in the mainstream of the...
This is really profound as you will agree. And if you want more details, you can ask her afterwards.
There is something in the Muslim Perspective of last month where...
Let me get one of those Qurans to explain to you what the deal is.
The preliminary information that you have is that there are 114 SURAs in the Quran.
29 of them are initialed with the Quranic initials, A. L. M., Q., N., S., K. H. Y., and so on,
these initials, 29 of them. The first initial, as you know, is in SURA number 2, verse number 1
that says A. L. M. The first one is in SURA number 2, verse 1.
And the last one is the initial N in SURA 68. Here it is. So, this part here of the book is what is
between the first initial and the last initial.
And what Lisa found in the last issue of the Muslim Perspective as published in that issue
was that between these two, the number of verses is a multiple of 19.
5263 between the first initial and the last initial. It's a multiple of 19. 19 x 277,
excluding the two false verses at the end of Sura number 9.
Also, between these, the first initial and the last initial, there are 19 groups
of initialed and uninitialed SURAs.
In other words, SURA 2 and 3 are initialed. That's one group.
SURAs 4, 5 and 6 are not initialed. That's group number two.
You go on like this, it's 19 groups.
So, what does this say?
This piece of information says that
the number of verses is a divine order dictated by God
because it conforms to the mathematical code.
Also, the sequence of SURAs
because the initialed, uninitialed and so on,
they alternate, making up 19 groups.
Now, last night, what she found was really profound
and has to do with the...
with this part here. Ok. Now, in the whole Quran,
the word Allah is a multiple of 19.
Allah is mentioned 2,698 times.
And God chose to put the first initial in Sura 2, the last initial in Sura 68.
So, what she did is add up the number, the word Allah that happened here; easier, she added the word Allah here in the smaller part.
SURA Al-Fãtehah before the A.L.M,
and from 69, SURA 68, I'm smiling for a reason.
Sura 68 has the letter N at the beginning.
So, counting the word Allah
outside this
came to 57.
Allah, the word Allah, outside, in this portion here
and in Sura Al-Fãtehah. There are two of them in SURA Al-Fãtehah.
Now, when she counted these verses,
you count from A.L.M, it's verse 1 of SURA 2
to the letter N, that's verse 1 of Sura 68 and you stop
because there are no initials after N.
So, the rest of SURA N is not counted in that
because it's inclusive.
Now, when you count the word Allah
in between here,
the difference is 2641.
You deduct this from the total number of Allah
which is also a multiple of 19, of course.
But God knows
that the people
who look at this... what does this tell us?
This tells us that the number of the verse
is dictated by God,
the number of the verse.
And if you look at Yusuf Ali, you will see that he changed the numbers because it sounded better to him.
You know, the numbering of verses is strange in some places and he couldn't take it
So, he played around with it.
Now, we wouldn't dare do that.
And in spite of the things that happened in the last 1400 years,
the Quran comes to us, unscaled
with the numbers of the verses exactly right.
I'm talking about the numbers of the verses and the numbers of the SURAs, as you will see before the end of this KHUTBA.
Ok, I was saying that when you count the verses you include, you start with the A.L.M. and you end with the N.
So, you have all of SURA 68
not counted in this because it is outside that range, verse-wise.
So, God knew that the unbelievers will say
why didn't you count the word Allah in SURA 68, also?
And we did or she did
and it is zero.
In SURA 68, there's not a single word Allah.
So, any way, any way they want to protest, God got their number: Zero
Their number is Zero.
So, I mean, it's really strange that a SURA as big as SURA 68 does not have any words Allah in it.
And I will complete this KHUTBA in the next section, IN SHAA ALLAH. Tooboo Ela Allah. Repent.
Alhamdu Lillah, Wa Ash-hadu Alla Elaha Ella Allah Wahdahu La Shareeka Lah.
This is only a small part of the great miracle that was discovered yesterday.
And I have been calling around the world this morning to spread the news out of here
because some people started the rumor that only the initialed chapters are guarded,
but this shows that
all the Quran is guarded because the word Allah is all over the place, as you know,
thousands of them.
And this portion here is outside the initialed area, if you wanna call it that.
And within the initialed area, we have 19 groups. Everything is so perfectly tight
that there is no hole for the disbelievers to escape.
And it is amazing that they continue to say
no. They continue to fail to see the miracle.
because God Himself said in Chapter 7 I will divert away from My miracles those who are too arrogant.
and no matter what kind of miracle you show them, they will not see it. God said that.
So, this is the explanation. Now, listen to this.
These 57 words, Allah, that are outside the initials that are here,
they happen in SURAs and verses, certain SURAs and certain verses.
And when you add the numbers of the SURAs and the verses where these happen, the total is 2432
2432. And this is 19 x 128.
Right. Now, this is a big number.
You add the numbers of the SURAs and the verses where the word Allah occurs
and you're gonna read this in the next issue of the Perspective.
Now, what does it tell us? This says the sequence of the SURAs is dictated by God,
the number of the SURAs, the number of the verses where the word Allah takes place, where the word Allah occurs
and it is so magnificent,
because there are verses where more than one Allah, you find 1 or 2 or 3
Allah in one verse,
but you cannot count the verse twice.
So, this system is so perfect
you have no doubt that you are reading the words of God, right here.
And when God says I put guards on you,
you know that there are guards on you.
So, you will not receive a scratch without God's control,
without deserving it or without a good reason for it
because sometimes God will mess up your life in order to have something good happen to you.
Joseph had to go to prison in order to rule Egypt afterwards.
He had to. So, going to prison was equivalent to going to school and graduating with a degree.
He graduated from the prison to rule Egypt.
So, even though the prison looked terrible, like a disaster,
it was to promote Joseph to a good position.
So, when God says I put guards on you,
when God speaks throughout Quran about invisible soldiers,
you know that He runs this world with invisible soldiers.
When God says that everything is written down
before the earth was created, everything was already recorded,
what you're gonna do next year is already recorded,
how many kids you're going to have is already recorded,
who they are going to marry is already written down,
what day and time and hour and place you're going to die is written down,
everything is written down, recorded. God says that.
And God says I'm telling you this so you don't feel sorry for the things you miss
and you don't get excited over the things you attain.
You have... the believer has an even keel.
He or she doesn't get excited or depressed
because everything is already recorded. There is nothing anybody can do,
but He guarantees victory for His people.
I mean to the point... I'm going to read for you Psalm 91 again,
which I read for you before.
And these were mathematically authenticated, too,
David's Psalms.
Now, we have evidence that the whole scripture,
we're talking about the original scripture,
was mathematically authenticated.
This Psalm happens to be confirmed in the Quran,
when God says I'll make you a King or Queen on Earth, you know that this is from God and you know that it is the absolute truth.
When God tells you I'm doing everything,
you know this is the absolute truth.
And when you pass the initial tests and you worship God regularly
and you do the 5 Prayers, certainty will come to you.
I'm smiling because this is something that we live every day.
We lived it today.
God was showing us that we are not doing anything,
even the words we utter.
God is doing everything and when He says this, you know that it is the absolute truth.
Here's Psalm 91, very quickly.
You who dwell in the shelter of the Most High,
This means every believer. It's talking to you.
Who abide in the shadow of the Almighty
You've decided to join God.
You abide in the shadow of the Almighty.
Say to the Lord, my refuge and my fortress,
This is what you said.
You decide to tell God my Lord, You're my refuge and my fortress.
For He will rescue you from the snare of the fowler.
From the destroying pestilence.
With His pinions, He will cover you.
Under His wings, you shall take refuge.
His faithfulness is a buckler and a shield.
One of God's names in the Quran is the Faithful.
When you tell God I'm gonna join You. I'm going to be with You. I'm gonna believe Your word. God is faithful to you.
And He will fulfill His part of the promise.
You happen to have no power and He has all the power. You can do nothing for God, but He can do everything for you.
Ok. David goes on and says with God's inspiration.
You shall not fear the terror of the night
and the arrow that flies by day.
You shall not fear the pestilence that roams in darkness,
nor the devastating plague at noon.
Though a thousand fall at your side
because of the AIDS disease. No, that's from me.
I mean, it will not touch you.
Though a thousand fall at your side; ten thousand at your right side.
Near you, it shall not come.
This is what God is saying. These are God's words that He reveals through David.
The Psalms were written by God
through David's mouth to teach us.
And you know every word in it is true.
It is confirmed by the Quran
and by this fantastic mathematical code whose parameters are increasing and the evidence is piling up beyond belief.
Rather with your eyes shall you behold and see the requital of the wicked.
As a person of God, you're gonna see that the people who are unjust to you, they're gonna get it, sooner or later.
And the Quran repeats it. Even if you don't see it, they will get it.
God will let you know.
You know, they may persecute you until the last week of your life and you may not see it.
This is why the Quran says whether you see it or not, they will get it. But if you're alive, you will see it. God will let you know.
Because you have the Lord for your refuge,
you have made the Most Hight your stronghold.
I mean, God controls Ronald Reagan, your boss.
The president of your company is God. Really! And He runs it.
When the president of the company gives you a raise,
God is really the One who is... I mean, God manipulates the president of your company.
When the president of your company reprimands you,
God is really doing that. He controls this man's or this woman's heart and mind.
So, because you have the Lord for your refuge, you have made the Most High your stronghold.
No evil shall befall you; nor shall affliction come near your tent.
You know that these words are God's words that are proven mathematically.
You have confidence.
Like this Moses throwing down the staff and became a snake, now you have confidence that this is the truth.
Now, you have tangible physical proof that this is true.
And you have... you better believe it.
Now, listen this is how the mechanism is.
Listen to this.
For to His angels, He has given command about you
that they guard you in all your ways,
Upon their hands, they shall bear you up,
lest you dash your foot against the stone.
They're gonna carry you up like this on their hands
if you're gonna dash your foot against the stone.
You better believe that. God is saying it. It is proven mathematically.
Lest you dash your foot against the stone.
You're walking in the night and there's a stone, you're gonna hit it, you don't see it,
and the angels will carry you or will remove the stone.
This is what God does.
Everything in this world is done by angels. I mean, by God, but I mean through His angels.
Aqem Al-Salat
Allahu Akbar Allahu Akbar